They Take War To A New Dimension.
Zone Troopers is a action, adventure, science
fiction film directed by Danny Bilson.
American soldiers, led by The Sarge, are stuck behind Nazi enemy lines.
As they make their way across the Italian countryside, they come across
an alien spaceship that has crash-landed in the woods.
The alien pilot is dead, but one of the ship's passengers is on the loose.
As the GIs hunt down the alien by splitting into smaller groups, they're not only tracked by the
Nazis, but also a whole host of other aliens come to save their stranded party.
The Sarge, played by Tim Thomerson.
Joey, played by Tim Van Patten.
Mittens, played by Art LaFleur.
Dolan, played by Biff Manard.
The Alien, played by William Paulson.
Col. Manheim, played by Peter Boom.
Zone Troopers is a 1985 American World War II science fiction film
directed by Danny Bilson and starring Tim Thomerson.
It was filmed in Italy by Empire Pictures with
Charles Band as executive producer.
The original music score was composed by Richard Band.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, nazi, italy, world war ii, hand grenade.
The tone is thought_provoking.